http://www.audiorecordingschool.com/privacy.html

Our website has moved, click here to visit our new site at CRAS.edu
Privacy Policy
The Conservatory of Recording Arts & Sciences – CRAS, understands your concerns about privacy. We want you to understand what types of information we collect on this site and what may happen to that information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at:
The Conservatory of Recording Arts & Sciences 2300 East Broadway Road, Tempe, AZ 85282 1.800.562.6383
Collection of information registrationand use of information
No user is required to provide information in order to visit CRAS’s site. However, a user must register in order to be placed on CRAS’s Email News Service list and other interactive services. In addition, a user must register to enter contests and other promotions. During registration, a user provides certain categories of information, such as name, address, email address, date of birth, and information regarding that user's application for enrolment, purchase of CRAS merchandise or other services. The information that you supply to CRAS enables us to customize our site to your interests and enhance your overall experience at our site. In addition, it helps us communicate with you about CRAS news and events. Besides sending you CRAS Email News, CRAS may use your contact information periodically in order to send you email regarding upcoming CRAS events. In addition, we may request information for other specific purposes. If the information provided will be used in any way that differs from the treatment outlined in this Privacy Policy, we will identify the differences when we request the information.
We use the personal information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking applications, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our news and offerings, and providing you with information from and about CRAS. From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our “Select Partners.” In such cases we might share and cross–reference information, including personal information about you that will enable these Select Partners to contact you regarding products and or services that may be of interest to you.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, at our events or through other correspondence with us. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross–reference with our Select Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your experiences with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.
If, at any time, you are receiving information from CRAS or its Select Partners that you no longer wish to receive, you may contact us to opt out and to request that your name be removed from a contact list. We pledge to honor all such requests and to affirm that our Select Partners do so as well.
Third party links and use of information
The CRAS site contains links to sites operated by third parties. These sites may collect personally identifiable information about you. For example, CRAS participates in the Google AdSense program and the interest-based advertising program offered by Google. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to service visitors to the CRAS site. In particular, Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to CRAS’s site visitors based on their visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Information transmitted does not include your name, address, email address, or telephone number. Visitors to CRAS’s site may opt out of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy page at this link.
Unless otherwise specifically stated herein, this Privacy Policy does not cover third-party data collection practices and CRAS does not assume any responsibility for third parties, even if you are linked to those sites through the CRAS website. Please check the privacy policy at each site you visit.
Passive collection of information
In addition to the information that you actively provide to CRAS, such as what you provide when you enter an application, CRAS collects information about how you interact with our site. CRAS collects passive information for purposes such as testing and improving a user's experience at the site and for compiling broad aggregate demographic data and related usage data for CRAS’s internal purposes. The types of passive information include, but are not limited to, your IP address, which type of browser you are using, where you go on our site and how long you stay on any part of our site. We may also track how you interact with our site, by assigning a random string of numbers and characters to your session. Passive information does not identify you to CRAS by name, and CRAS does not link your IP address to your personally identifiable information.
We use a "cookie" based data collection paradigm in certain areas of our site. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services; for example, the use of cookies allows us to reduce the frequency with which you will need to enter your password on password-protected areas of our site. Additionally, in some cases, certain functionalities are only feasible through the use of a cookie. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site and/or you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.
Collection of information from children
CRAS abides by federal law and the guidelines set up by the Federal Trade Commission regarding youth privacy. As such, CRAS will not knowingly collect any personal information from young people under the age of 13, unless CRAS provides notice that such information is being collected and obtains verifiable parental consent.
Sharing of information
Other than on the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy, CRAS pledges that it will not sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information without your permission. CRAS may, however, share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information, which can identify any individual user. While CRAS strives to protect the personal information of our users, CRAS will release personal information if required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary.
Security
CRAS has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. CRAS protects personally identifiable information to the extent reasonably feasible by utilizing both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and restricted physical access to the places where your information is stored. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, and our security procedures are regularly reviewed and revised, if necessary.
Other provisions
Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy--Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such usage. CRAS reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to customers or site visitors.
If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner which materially differs from the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by promptly updating the posted Privacy Policy and you will have an opportunity to opt out from further communications In addition, if we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our site notifying users that our Privacy Policy has changed. In some cases when we post such a notice, we will also send an email to users who have provided their information notifying them of the changes in our Privacy Policy.
Choice/Opt-out—CRAS users are asked to give information to be put on CRAS’s Email News Service list, apply for admission, or to receive commercial email regarding upcoming CRAS promotions and events. If you receive CRAS’s commercial email and would like to avoid receiving such email in the future, you may opt-out of receiving it by clicking on the opt-out (unsubscribe) area within that email.
CRAS will only communicate with you according to your instructions. Your privacy is important to CRAS. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please contact us via the contact information listed above.
CRAS GradCareer Opportunities
Recording engineer
- Music
- Soundtracks
Game audio designer
- Video games
- Apps
- Mobile audio
- Lectures
And more!
CRAS PEOPLEMAKE IT
Overview
Music
Live Sound
Film & TV
Video Game
THE PROGRAM
Overview
Laptop Recording Pkg.
Course Outline
Certifications
Guest Lecturers
Internship
Faculty
Gainful Employment
ADMISSIONS
Overview
Site Map
©2013 Conservatory of Recording Arts and Sciences.CRAS is a registered trademark of the Conservatory of Recording Arts & Sciences.All rights reserved.
Gilbert Campus: 1205 North Fiesta Boulevard, Gilbert, AZ 85233 480.858.9400 | Tempe Campus: 2300 East Broadway Road, Tempe, AZ 85282 480.858.0764
